

Lahiru Dinelka

Software Engineer

+94 77 011 4496

devlahirudinelka.github.io

devlahirudinelka@gmail.com

Malabe, Sri lanka.

About Me

I am a Software Engineer with robust problem-solving skills and proven experience in creating and designing software in a test driven environment. I recognize myself as A dedicated and energetic person with decent analytical and problem-solving skills and motivated to undertake any project, Software based. I would like to explore and learn new technologies while adapting to the working environment and to be an asset to the company.

Expertise

- Mobile App Development
- Full-stack Development
- UI / UX Development
- Game Development
- Web Development
- Blender
- Web Apps
- SASS Development
- Blockchain
- Smart Contract

Experience

Frontend Developer

Part-Time

Sphiria Digital Studio I Kandy | Jun 2023 - Present

REST APIs · User Experience (UX) · Redux,js · Tailwind CSS · Figma (Software) · Git · Next,js · Vue,js · Web Development · Full-Stack Development · Node,js · Front-End Development · Mobile Application Development · Python (Programming Language) · Blockchain · Web Design · Front-end Development · Mobile Applications · Software Development · JavaScript · Flutter · C++ · React,js

Trainee Frontend Developer

Contract

Synacal | Remote | Mar - May | 2023

User Experience (UX) \cdot WordPress

Frontend Developer

Part-Time

Faith & Hope Pvt. Ltd. | Colombo | Jan 2023 - Present

REST APIs · User Experience (UX) · Redux.js · Tailwind CSS · Ionic Framework · Vue.js · React Native · AngularJS · JavaScript · React.js

Software Engineer

Full-Time

Artslab Creatives | Havelock | Dec 2022 - Present

REST APIs · User Experience (UX) · Tailwind CSS · Three.js · Blender · Digital Marketing · Git · Web Development · WordPress · Laravel · FullStack Development · Front-End Development · Mobile Application Development · Web Design · Software Development · Flutter · C++ · React.js · PHP

Project Manager

Full-Time

CodeTech Lk | Remote | Aug - Nov | 2022

 $\mathsf{Jira} \cdot \mathsf{Slack} \cdot \mathsf{Trello} \cdot \mathsf{Project} \ \mathsf{Managment}$

Web Developer

Full-Time

CodeTech Lk | Remote | Feb - Aug | 2022

REST APIs · User Experience (UX) · Redux.js · Tailwind CSS · Figma (Software) · Git · Next.js · Vue.js · Web Development · Full-Stack Development · Node.js · Front-End Development · Mobile Application Development · Python (Programming Language) · Blockchain · Web Design · Front-end Development · Mobile Applications · Software Development · JavaScript · Flutter · C++ · React.js

Technical Skills

Coding Languages Skills

C, C++, Java, JavaScript, HTML/CSS, Kotlin. PHP, TypeScript, Solidity, Blockchain, Redux

Frameworks / Systems Skills

Bootstrap, SASS, React, React-Native, Flutter, Angular, Vue, Material UI, NextJs, WordPress, ThreeJS, EloectoneJS

Database Skills

My SQL, MS SQL Server, MongoDB, SQLite, Firebase, PostgreSQL, Microsoft Azure

Back End Skills

Express.js, Node.JS, Laravel

Operating System Skills

Windows, Kali Linux

Coding environment Skills

Android Studio, Visual Studio Code

Other Skills

Eclipse, NetBeans, MS Office, Adobe Dreamweaver, XAMPP, VMware Workstation, NPM, YARN, pub.dev, Blender

Reference

 Dr. Gayana Fernando Senior Lecturer, (Higher Grade)
SLIIT Academy.

(+94) 117543600 gayana.f@sliit.lk

Miyuru Dharmage

Chief Software Engineer Artslab Creatives

(+94) 77 439 5913 miyuru@dev.artslabcreatives.com

Education

Advanced Level

Sri Rahula National School I Alawwa | 2018

Completed G.C.E Advanced Level Examination successfully.

Computer Sci. & Software Engineering

SLIIT Academy | Kollupitiya | 2019-2022

B.Sc. Computer Science and Software Engineering

Certifications

Flutter and Dart to create Android and IOS Udemy - 2021

Adobe XD Essential Training: Design

LinkedIn Learning · Course Certificate - 2021

Android Development Essential Training: 1

LinkedIn Learning · Course Certificate - 2021

Android Development Essential Training: 2

LinkedIn Learning · Course Certificate - 2021

Flutter

LinkedIn Learning · Course Certificate - 2021

Kotlin Essential Training

LinkedIn Learning · Course Certificate -2021

React.js Essential Training

LinkedIn Learning · Course Certificate - 2021

The Fundamentals of Digital Marketing

Google Digital Garage - 2020

The Complete React Developer

Udemy 2021